Guide to Peter P. Carr Papers RG.055
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series XIV: D3 Non BS Path Dependent, 1990-2004
  - Applications for Calculating Bonds & Integrals, 2002-01-19-2002-01-22 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Applications to MC Simulations, 2002-01-24 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - What is an Adjoint?, 2002-02-03-2002-02-12 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Application to Semi-Static Hedging, 2001-07-13-2002-01-26 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Manuscript - Put Call Reversal, 2002-03-24 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Replicating Portfolios in Heston Using Stock, Bond & Variable Susps, 2004-11-20-2004-11-21 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - D3 for Cnr Touches, 2004-07-03-2004-07-07 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Signing Delta, Gamma and Vega of a Call in the Heston Model, 2004-02-09 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Equations at Change of Dependent Variable to GT, 2004-07-03-2004-07-13 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - D3 for Time Homogenous Markov Processes, 2004-02-03-2004-07-07 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - DCC Greeks, 2004-07-03-2004-11-20 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Symmetries in Heston Model, 2004-11-18 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - HBKOG - Greek Calculation Methods, 2004-10-07-2004-11-20 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - American Options Greeks, 1999-08-13-2002-07-05 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Asians Greeks, 1999-08-22 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Burner Claims Greeks, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Operator Solution for Claims Paying G(J) at fpt to Barrier, 1999-08-23-1999-09-06 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Envelope Theorem, 2002-07-12 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Signing Delta, Gamma & Vega of a Call in the Heston Model, 2004-02-03 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Rate Greeks for Single Barrier Options, 1999-06-20 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - UIC Greeks, 1999-08-27-1999-09-06 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - General Payoff at fpt of GBM, 1999-08-06 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - FPT PDF for ABM, 1999-08-18-1999-09-04 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Barrier Option Integration, 1999-08-23 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - CJM, 1990-08 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Conference Submission, 1992-03-19-1993-04-08 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - FD's to Get Greeks at Americans, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Fugit Derivation & Financial Interpretation of Fugit, 1999-06-20-1999-08-26 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Greeks when Vol is a Function of S & t, 1999-06-20 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Lewis, Keith; Option Pricing Using Levy Process, 2000-01 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Levy Processes, 2000-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lookback Options Greeks, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Deriving Derivatives of Derivative Securities, 1999-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Power Claim, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Spatially Dep. Vol., 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Spatial Derivatives when Vol. Satisfies PDE, 1999-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - State Variable Results, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Stochastic Perturbation Analysis, 2000-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Stochastic Vol., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Deriving Derivatives of Derivative Securities Notes, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Series XV: Determining Volatility Surfaces, 1998-2000
  - Determining Volatility Surfaces and Option Values from an Implied Volatility Smile, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - World Scientific, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence with Thaleia/Team, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Calculations on Volatility Surfaces, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Adding or Subtracting a Positive Constant from Sinh Process, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Affix Drift Transformation to SBM, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Bonded Stock Payoffs, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Calibration, 2000-02-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Call Valuation, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Change of Measure Plus Change of Stock Variables, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Comments on Volatility Surfaces Talk, 1998-09-25; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Conflicted Div. Function, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Concentration Dependent Diffusion Media, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Cons'n & Portfolio Problem, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - D-Dimensional Driver, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - D^3 Calculations, 1998-08-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Examples of Terminal Vol. Smiles, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Forward Propagation, 1998-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Fourier Transforms, 1999-02-26; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Gamma Functions, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Implying Payoff Function, 1998-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Intended Integrals of CDF, 1998-08-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Linear Absolute Vol., 1998-08-22; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Logger as Solution to Heat Equation, 1998-08-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Lover Knockout Barnier for Equity, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Martingales/Polynomials, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Mill's Ratio, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Modelling Vol./Gamma, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Multiplicatively Separable Solutions, 1998-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - (Application to) Numerical Methods, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - One Dimenional Diffusion, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Operator Calculus, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - PCS with Vol. Smiles, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - (Using) Other Assets Besides Stock to Get W, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Pure Jump Processes as Driver, 1998-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Recovery from Value, Vol., Divs, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Rel. Vol. as a Function of C, Power of S or F Including Power=1, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - RN PDF as Function of S or DF, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Rel. Vol. as Function of Spot or Found, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Rel. Vol. as Function of x=InF, x=InS, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Specifying Log of Spot, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Stochastic Local Vol. Surface Derived from a Stochastic Local Vol. Smile, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Stock Payoff Functions, Even Functions, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Stock Payoff Functions Monotonic, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Stock Pricing Function as Solution to Heat Equation, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Stock Valuation, 1998-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Stock Price as Expected Value of PCS Payoff of T^1, 1998-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Stock Vol. is a Derivative Security, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Strike Interpolation & Extrapolation, 1998-07-28; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Time and/or Space Dep. Firm Vol., 1998-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Time Homogenous Diffusion as Driver, 1998-08-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - To DC, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - A Transformation of Abs Vol. Written as a Function of InS, 1998-08-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Transformation to OU Process, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 84)
- Series XVI: Diffusions, 1989-2002
  - Arcsinh-normal Model Results, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Asset Correspondences in Backward & Forward Economy, 2002-06-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - (Using) Backward SDE's, 2001-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Backward Running SBM, 2001-07-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Bayes Rule for Getting q^, 2001-11-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - BC PDE (in forward time), 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - BP^ PDE, 2001-07-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - BS Model Results, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - (Proof of) Butterfly Spot Duality, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Calibrating to Discrete Maturity Vol. Smiles Using Call Consistency, 2001-06-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Call Consistency, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Carrying Cost Duality, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Constant Elasticity of Variance (CEV), 1989-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Changing Measure Without Reversing Time, 2000-11-18; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Changing Variables, 2002-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Chapman Kolmogorov Interpretation, 2001-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 100)
- Series XVII: Diffusion Time Reversal and European Options, 2000-2002
  - Constant Normal Vol. Model, 2001-07-11-2002-06-19 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Conventions, 2001-07-18-2001-08-08 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Delta Hedging Interpretations (in Forward & Backward Time), 2001-07-18-2002-06-27 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Deriving q^ Dynamics from q Dynamics, 2001-07-05-2002-01-30 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Delta=1/2 Characteristic, 2002-02-09 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Discretization, 2000-08-04-2001-08-08 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Displaced Diffusion Counterexample, 2001-07-14 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - PCS Holding Locally to PCR?, 2001-07-08 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Deciding Between Maturity Spreading & Maturity Randomization, 2001-08-04 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Duality, 2000-11-08-2002-01-22 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Duality in Elliott's Book, Undated (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Duality Between Strike Randomization & Strike Diversification, 2001-08-04 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Forward & Backward PDE's as MG Condition on Image & Real Part, 2001-05-28-2001-07-28 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - (Deriving & Interpreting the) Forward Call PDE, 1999-11-08-2002-02-03 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - FC PDE, 2000-09-21-2002-01-29 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - FC PDE to Probabilistic Interpretation, 2001-06-16-2001-08-04 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - FC PDE (KFE-Kolmogorov Forward Equation), 2001-06-26-2001-08-01 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Forward Equations in Fixed Income, 2002-09-05 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - From Forward Price as Underlying to Spot, 2001-07-23 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Gamma Induced Backward Running Process, 2002-03-19-2002-03-24 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Generating New Closed Form Solutions from Old Ones via Time Reversal, 2001-07-19 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Geometry of Time Reversal, 2002-01-19-2002-01-22 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Jesper's Dissertation Discussion in Time Reversal, 2001-07-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Jesper Email, 2002-03-18; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Journal Submission, 2002-03-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Line Integral Proof of PER, 2002-02-22; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Kit Hybrid PDEs, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Derivation of KBE & KFE, 2000-12-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - KFE Derivations, 2000-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - KFE from KBE, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Markov Property Assn., 2002-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Measure Changes, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - No Arb, Markov F>, Mg in Reverse Time, 2000-2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Numerical Tests of PCR, 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Moving Time Backward in Backwards Clock, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Overview, 2000-2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Pathwise Relationship Between SIS^, 2001-07-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - PCR Under Trans'ns, 2001-07-14; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - PCR via Implied Vol, 2002-02-22; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - PCS, 2001-07-14; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - PDE in S & K, 2001-07-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 141)
  - Philosophy, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - Proof of Equality of Probs, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 143)
  - Proof of PCR, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 144)
  - Put Call Equivalence, 2002-06-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 145)
  - Quantering, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 146)
  - Reversed SDE, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 147)
  - Relationship of Stock Process to Stock Price Process - Assessing Measures Change Only, 2001-07-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 148)
  - Results in Terms of Forwards Under Pos r, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 149)
  - Semi Group Viewpoint, 2001-07-28; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 150)
  - Single Stock Replication of European Call When Vol Time & Spatially Dependent, 2001-07-16; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 151)
  - Sin Function, 2001-07-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 152)
  - Space-Time Integrals of Calls, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 153)
  - Spatially Dependent Carrying Costs, 2002-02-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 154)
  - SIT Hybrid PDE, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 155)
  - Starting Stochastic, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 156)
  - Stochastic Time Change & Time Reversal, 2001-07-31; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 157)
  - Strike Process is Recip. of Reversal Stock Price Process (Wrong Lognormal Vol), 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Strike Maturity Relationship Among Standard European Options, 2001-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 159)
  - Strike is Neg. of Reversal Spot (Possibly Translated) (Wrong), 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 160)
  - Strike Price is a Function of Stock Price, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - (Forward PDE in) SV Models, 2000-07-20; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - Time Integral Representations of Option Values, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Time Reversed Process S^, 2001-07-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Time Reversability of Semi-Martingales, 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Time Reversal Using Stratonovich Integral, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - Value Consistency, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Why Dissect at q?, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 168)
- Series XVIII: Diffusion Transformation, 1998-2000
  - Application of Symmetry in Finance, 2000-07-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Closed Form Option Valuation with Smiles, 1999-2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Diffusion Transformation Notes (1), 2000-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Doob's H Transform, 2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Azema & Yor, Sur Les Zeros des Martingales Continues, Semi Prob. XXVI, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Martingales Vanishing with SBM, 2000-02-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Laplace Transformation of E 0 (WT), Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Implied as a Function of Local Vol. under PI, 2000-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Some Even Models in PI Class, 2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Spatial Derivatives, 2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Doob's H Transforms via FT, 2000-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Soluble Drifts, 1999-2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - X Explicit in S Only, 1999-2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - From Local Vol. to Option Prices, 1999-2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Gamma Closed Form Option Vol'n with Smiles, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - R^3 as Driver, 2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Consistency with (ln(k/F)/sigmaT) Behavior, 2000-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Downward Displaced GBM, 2000-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Generic Call Pricing Formula, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Trader's Derivation of PDE for s, 1999-01-26; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Stock Price as Function of W^sh's Instead of W, 1998-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Noninvertible but Integrable Payoff Functions, 1999-02-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Alex Lipton Notes, 2000-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Lie Group Analysis of Parabolic Normal Form, 2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Options & Other Nonlinear Operators as a Lie Algebra, 2000-04-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Lie Groups, Time Integrals & American Options, 2000-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Multivariable Diffusion & Lie Groups, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Diffusion Transformation Notes (2), 2000-02-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Bivariable Binary in 3 Parameter Arcsinh, 2000-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Goldenberg in Arcsinhnormal Model, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Calibration of Arcsinhnormal, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Closed Form Valuation of Compound Options in the Arcsinhnormal Model, 2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Absorbing Sinh Stock Price Processes, 1998-07-01-2000-02-07 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Callable Call in Arcsinh Model, 1999-11-10-2000-01-09 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Interpretation of x + a in 3 Parameter Arcsinh, 2000-01-18 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Share Economy in Arcsinhnormal Model, 2000-01-08-2000-01-31 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Time Dependent CU as Driver, 2000-02-04 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Hyperbolas, 2000-01-31 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Three Parameter Arcsinhnormal, 1999-01-13-2000-02-05 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Delta in 3 Parameter Arcsinhnormal Model, 2000-01 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - CU as Driver, 2000-02-03 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Coth Drift, 2000-01-22-2000-02-01 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Bivariate Normal in Matlab, 2000-01-02-2000-02-10 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - He Mchem Approach to ID Diffusions, 2000-02-18-2000-02-27 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Scale Function & Probabilities Hitting Flat Boundaries, 1998-09-06-1998-09-08 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Speed Measures, 1999-10-03 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Static Hedging & Scale Function, 1998-08-14 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Series XIX: Double Barriers, 1992-2000
  - Kunitomo & Ikeda, Pricing Options with Curved Boundaries, 1992-10 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Rogers & Stapleton, Fast Accurate Binomial Pricing, Finance & Stochastics, 1997-02 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Sbuelz, A.; Semi-Static Hedging of Double Barrier Options, Tilburg University Working Paper, 2000-07 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Single Barrier Valuations, 1994-11-1995-07-31 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Stability, Undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Static Hedging, 1999-06-30-1999-07-01 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Financial Interpretation of Double Knockouts, Undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Input Spec's, 1994-05-17 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Kunitomo/Ikeda, Pricing Options with Curved Boundaries, 1992-06-1994-11-16 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Method of Lines Workshop, 1995-04-24 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - MCL Valuation of Single Barriers, 1994-05 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Method of Images, 1994-08 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Plots, Undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Proposal, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Timbrell, Richard, 1994-05-16 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Richard Skora's Two Barrier Options, 1993-09-08-1993-09-18 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Term Structure, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Time Discretization, Undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Fugit of Perpetual Double Barrier, 1999-10-03 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Analytic Formula, Undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Barrier Randomization, Undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Binomial Correction & Aitken's O^2, Undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Binomial Valuation of Double Knockout, 1994-07 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Chernavsky, Alex, 1994-10-26 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Chase Double Knockin/out, Undated (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Double Knockout Call - Global, 1994-1995-07-20 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Double Knockout Call - Local, Undated (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Double Knockout Put - Global, 1995-07-20 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Double Knockout Put - Local, Undated (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Embedded Ocufile Barriers, 1994-06-30 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Interpolation, Undated (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Series XX: Double Knockouts by Fourier, 1994-1998
  - Correspondence from Ravi Bhagavatula, 1997-06-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Double-Knockout Rewrite, 1997-1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - C PGMs, 1994-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence with Ravi & Others, 1994-1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Extensions, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Variance Term Structure Figures, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Journal Submission Mathematical Finance, 1994-1995; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Valuing Double Barrier Options with Time-Dependent Parameters, 1995-1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Ravi's Earlier Work, 1992-1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Ravi's Resume, 1994-1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Referee Reports, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Section 3: Valuation Constant Parameters, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Time Dependent Rebates, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Section 4: Valuation with Time Dependent Parameters, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Section 5.1 Convergence Issues, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Section 5.2 Term Structure Effects, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 92)
- Series XXI: Early Exercise Results, 1989-1992
  - American Put, 1990-1992; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Approximations, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Arbitraging Mispricing, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - American Option Problem, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Binomial Model, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Bob's Notes, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Calculus of Variations, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Calculation of Boundary, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Current Version of Carr Jarrow, 1989-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Characterizing the Boundary, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Characterization of Early Exercise, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Copies of Carr Jarrow, 1989-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Corrections to Carr-Myneni, 1989-09-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Current version of Carr Myneni, 1989-09-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Derivatives, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Differentiability at Boundary, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Discretizing Over Stock Prices, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dividends, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Envelope Theorem, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Equivalence of Cox Ross and Carr Jarrow for European Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Equivalence of McKeon & Carr, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Equivalence of McKeon & Myneni, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Equivalence of Carr & Myneni, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - European Call Valuation Under GBM, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - European Put Valuation Under GBM, 1989-09-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Exponential Spline, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Extensions/Improvements, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Extreme Values, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - First Passage Time Density to Boundary, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Fourier Solution of PDE, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Futures Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Geometric Brownian Motion, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Geske Johnson in the Bin Model, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 25)